https://admissions.rutgers.edu/privacy-policy

Menu
AcademicsFind Your MajorCampus LifeApplyingHow to ApplyApplication UpdatesAdmissions ProfileMore for First-Year ApplicantsMore for Transfer ApplicantsMore for International ApplicantsMore for Part-Time & Non-Degree ApplicantsPaying for CollegeNJ Tuition EligibilityNJ Educational Opportunity Fund (EOF)Financial Aid GlossarymyRutgers DashboardFor CounselorsContactJoin Our Mailing ListVisitPre-College ProgramsRutgers Stories
Privacy Policy
Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey, is committed to protecting the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information to the extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Personally identifiable information is not actively shared by the Office of Undergraduate Admissions other than under one or more of the following circumstances: as required by laws that guarantee public access to certain types of information; in response to subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize access; for use by a trusted third-party partner to market the university on our behalf; or for use by internal constituents to administer university functions. In particular, we do not sell personal information collected on our web servers.
Information Collected
Use of Collected Information
Distribution of Collected Information
Individual Choice
Responsibility for Linked-To Sites
SMS Terms & Conditions
Information Collected
The Office of University Undergraduate Admissions may collect personal information such as name, address, email address, telephone number(s), and/or educational interests. Such personal information may be requested by us for administrative purposes. Additional personal information, such as credit card account information, may be requested for application or enrollment purposes.
Web servers typically collect, at least temporarily, the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; web pages requested; referring web page; browser used; date and time. The Office of University Undergraduate Admissions may collect statistics identifying particular IP addresses from which our websites are accessed.
Use of Collected Information
The Office of University Undergraduate Admissions may use IP address information and anonymous browser history to report information about site accesses and for profiling purposes. This information is generally used to improve web presentation and utilization. The Office of University Undergraduate Admissions also may use IP address information for troubleshooting purposes.
Some Office of University Undergraduate Admissions online activity sites may use "cookies" in order to deliver web content specific to individual users’ interests or to keep track of online purchasing transactions. Sensitive personal information is not stored within cookies.
We may use personal information collected from websites for the purpose of future communication in order to keep you informed of programs, events and other offerings.
We may use outside vendors to provide certain marketing services on our behalf, such as email distribution, mail fulfillment, and digital web advertising. These third-party vendors will have access to the information needed to perform their functions.
Distribution of Collected Information
The Office of University Undergraduate Admissions will not disclose, without your consent, personal information collected about you, except for certain explicit circumstances in which disclosure is required by law or is necessary for a trusted third-party partner to provide certain marketing services on our behalf.
We will not sell personal information to third-party organizations.
Individual Choice
Individuals who wish to use methods other than online enrollment may submit requests by email or U.S. mail addressed to the Office of University Undergraduate Admissions.
Access to your own information: Questions regarding users’ rights to review, modify or delete their previously provided personal information should be directed to the campus organization to which they provided the information. Any disputes will be resolved under existing records regulations applicable to the Office of University Undergraduate Admissions.
Responsibility for Linked-To Sites
While using an Office of University Undergraduate Admissions website, you may encounter hypertext links to the web pages of organizations not directly affiliated with the Office of University Undergraduate Admissions. The Office of University Undergraduate Admissions does not control the content or information practices of external organizations. We recommend you review the privacy statements of these organizations.
SMS Terms & Conditions
Rutgers University-Camden
Rutgers University-Newark
Rutgers University-New Brunswick
Take the Next Step
Apply
Visit Rutgers
Find Your Major
